<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.khangman.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <name>KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">الشنق</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਕੇਹੈਂਗਮੈਨ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KWisielec</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Hänga gubben</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">K Adam Asmaca</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKHangManxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KHangMan</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">語言_KHangMan</name>
  <summary>Hangman Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">لعبة الرجل المشنوق</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Igra vješala</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Joc del penjat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Joc del penjat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Hra Hangman</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Galgespillet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Buchstabierspiel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Κρεμάλα</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Hangman Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Pendumisto-Ludo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juego del ahorcado</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Poomismäng</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Urkatuaren jokoa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Hirsipuupeli</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Jeu de pendu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">O xogo do aforcado</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">משחק איש תלוי</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Akasztófajáték</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Joco Hangman</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Permainan Hangman (Algojo)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gioco dell'impiccato</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">თამაში Hangman</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">행맨 게임</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Budelio žaidimas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nds">Galgenmanntje-Speel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Het spel Galgje</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Hengdmann-spel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਕੇਹੈਂਗਮੈਨ ਖੇਡ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Gra w Wisielca</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Jogo do Enforcado</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogo da forca</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Joc de Spânzurătoare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Игра «Виселица»</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Hra Hangman</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Igra vislic</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Hänga gubben-spel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Adam Asmaca Oyunu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Гра Hangman</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxHangman Gamexx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">吊颈人游戏</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">劊子手（hangman）遊戲</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KHangMan is a game based on the well-known hangman game. It is aimed at children aged six and over. The game has several categories of words to play with, for example: Animals (animals words) and three difficulty categories: Easy, Medium and Hard. A word is picked at random, the letters are hidden, and you must guess the word by trying one letter after another. Each time you guess a wrong letter, part of a picture of a hangman is drawn. You must guess the word before being hanged! You have 10 tries.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">الشنق  هي لُعْبَة تعتمد على لعبة الرجل المشنوق المعروفة. إنها تستهدف الأطفال الذين تتراوح أعمارهم بين ستة أعوام وأكثر. تحتوي اللُعْبَة على عدة فئات من الكلمات للعب بها، على سبيل المثال: حيوانات (كلمات حيوانات) وثلاث فئات صعوبة: سهل ومتوسط وصعب. يتم انتقاء كلمة عشوائيًا، وتخفى الأحرف، ويجب أن تخمن الكلمة بواسطة تجرِبة حرف تلو الآخر. في كل مرة تخمن فيها حرف خاطئ سيرسم جزء من صورة الرجل المشنوق. يجب أن تخمن الكلمة قبل شنقك! لديك 10 محاولات.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">KHangMan je igra bazirana na poznatoj igri vješala. Namijenjena je djeci uzrasta od šest i više godina. Igra ima nekoliko kategorija riječi da se igraju, na primjer: Životinje (riječi životinje ) i tri težine kategorije: lakii, srednje i teško. Riječ je izabrananasumice, slova su skrivenae, i morate pogodite reč pokušavajući jedno slovoo za drugom. Svaki put kada probate pogrešno slovo,nacrta se dio obješenog.. Morate pogoditi riječ pre nego što je obješen! Imate 10 pokušaja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KHangMan és un joc basat en el conegut joc del penjat. Està dirigit a infants de 6 anys o més. El joc disposa de diverses categories de paraules amb les quals jugar, per exemple: Animals (noms d'animals) i tres nivells de dificultat: fàcil, mitjà i difícil. Es tria una paraula aleatòriament, les lletres resten ocultes i s'ha d'endevinar la paraula provant una lletra rere l'altra. Cada vegada que s'escriu una lletra errònia es va dibuixant la imatge del penjat. Haureu d'endevinar-la abans de quedar penjat! Disposareu de 10 intents.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KHangMan és un joc basat en el conegut joc del penjat. Està dirigit a infants de 6 anys o més. El joc disposa de diverses categories de paraules amb les quals jugar, per exemple: Animals (noms d'animals) i tres nivells de dificultat: fàcil, mitjà i difícil. Es tria una paraula aleatòriament, les lletres resten ocultes i s'ha d'endevinar la paraula provant una lletra rere l'altra. Cada vegada que s'escriu una lletra errònia es va dibuixant la imatge del penjat. Haureu d'endevinar-la abans de quedar penjat! Disposareu de 10 intents.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">KHangMan er et spil baseret på det velkendte galgespil. Målgruppen er børn på seks år og opefter. Spillet har adskillige kategorier af ord man kan lege med, f.eks. dyr (dyreord) og tre sværhedsgrader: Nem, mellem og svær. Et ord vælges tilfældigt og bogstaverne er skjulte, og du skal gætte ordet ved at prøve et bogstav ad gangen. Hver gang du gætter et forkert bogstav, tegnes en del af et billede af en galge. Du skal gætte ordet før du bliver hængt! Du har 10 forsøg.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KHangMan ist ein Spiel, das auf dem wohlbekannten Galgenmännchen basiert. Es ist ein Spiel für Kinder ab 6 Jahren mit verschiedenen Wort-Kategorien, zum Beispiel Tiere (Tiernamen) und weitere drei Kategorien mit unterschiedlichen Schwierigkeitsstufen: Leicht, Mittel und Schwer. Ein Wort wird zufällig ausgewählt, die Buchstaben verdeckt und Sie müssen das Wort raten, indem Sie einen Buchstaben nach dem anderen eingeben. Jedesmal, wenn Sie einen falschen Buchstaben eingeben, wird ein weiterer Teil des Galgenmännchens gezeichnet. Sie müssen das gesuchte Wort erraten, ehe das Galgenmännchen fertig gezeichnet ist! Dafür haben Sie 10 Versuche.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KHangMan είναι ένα παιχνίδι που βασίζεται στην πολύ γνωστή Κρεμάλα. Απευθύνεται σε παιδιά ηλικίας από έξι ετών και άνω. Το παιχνίδι περιλαμβάνει πολλές κατηγορίες λέξεων, για παράδειγμα: Ζώα (λέξεις με ζώα) και τρία επίπεδα δυσκολίας: εύκολο, μέσο και δύσκολο. Μια λέξη επιλέγεται τυχαία, τα γράμματα είναι κρυμμένα και εσείς πρέπει να μαντέψετε τη λέξη δοκιμάζοντας το ένα γράμμα μετά το άλλο. Κάθε φορά που μαντεύετε λάθος, σχεδιάζεται ένα τμήμα της εικόνας της κρεμάλας. Πρέπει να μαντέψετε τη λέξη πριν κρεμαστείτε! Έχετε 10 προσπάθειες.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KHangMan is a game based on the well-known hangman game. It is aimed at children aged six and over. The game has several categories of words to play with, for example: Animals (animals words) and three difficulty categories: Easy, Medium and Hard. A word is picked at random, the letters are hidden, and you must guess the word by trying one letter after another. Each time you guess a wrong letter, part of a picture of a hangman is drawn. You must guess the word before being hanged! You have 10 tries.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">KHangMan estas ludo bazita sur la konata pendumul-ludo. Ĝi celas infanojn de ses jaroj kaj pli. La ludo havas plurajn kategoriojn de vortoj por ludi, ekzemple: Bestoj (bestaj vortoj) kaj tri malfacilecaj kategorioj: Facila, Meza kaj Malfacila. Vorto estas elektita hazarde, la literoj estas kaŝitaj, kaj vi devas diveni la vorton provante unu literon post alia. Ĉiufoje kiam vi divenas malĝustan leteron, parto de bildo de pendumulo estas desegnita. Vi devas diveni la vorton antaŭ esti pendigita! Vi havas 10 provojn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KHangMan es un juego basado en el conocido pasatiempo del ahorcado. Está dirigido a niños de seis años o más. El juego tiene varias categorías de palabras con las que jugar, como: Animales (palabras relacionadas con animales) y tres categorías de distinta dificultad: fácil, media y difícil. Se selecciona una palabra de forma aleatoria, las letras se ocultan y se debe adivinar la palabra una letra tras otra. Cada vez que se falla en una letra, se dibuja una parte de la imagen del ahorcado. ¡Tienes que adivinar la palabra antes de que te cuelguen! Tienes 10 intentos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KHangMan tugineb tuntud poomismängule. See on mõeldud enam kui kuueaastastele lastele. Mängul on neli raskusastet (loomad ehk loomanimed, lihtne, keskmine ja raske). Sõna valitakse juhuslikult, tähed on peidetud ning sul tuleb sõna tähti ükshaaval pakkudes ära arvata. Iga kord, kui pakud vale tähe, joonistatakse poomispildile kriipsuke juurde. Nii et parem arva sõna ära, enne kui pooja oma tegevusega lõpule jõuab! Pakkuda saab 10 korda.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KHangMan urkatuaren joko ezagunean oinarritutako jokoa bat da. Sei urte edo gehiagoko haurrei zuzendua dago. Jokoak jolasteko hainbat hitz-kategoria ditu, adibidez: animaliak (animalien hitzak) eta hiru zailtasun-kategoria: erraza, ertaina eta zaila. Hitz bat ausaz aukeratzen da, letrak ezkutuan daude, eta hitza asmatu behar duzu letra bat bestearen atzetik probatuz. Okerreko letra hautatzen duzun bakoitzean, urkatu baten irudiaren atal bat marrazten da. Urkatu aurretik hitza asmatu behar duzu! 10 saiakera dituzu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KHangMan perustuu tunnettuun hirsipuupeliin ja on suunnattu kuusivuotiaille sekä sitä vanhemmille lapsille. Pelissä on useita pelattavia sanaryhmiä kuten esimerkiksi eläimet (eläinsanat) sekä kolme vaikeusryhmää: helppo, keskitaso and vaikea. Sana valitaan satunnaisesti, kirjaimet piilotetaan, ja pelaajan täytyy arvata sana yrittämällä yhtä kirjainta toisen jälkeen. Jokaisesta väärin arvatusta kirjaimesta piirretään seuraava osa hirsipuuhun. Sana täytyy arvata ennen kuin tulee hirtetyksi! Pelissä on 10 yritystä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KHangMan est un jeu de pendu. Il est conçu pour les enfants de six ans et plus. Le jeu offre plusieurs catégories de mots, par exemple les animaux, et trois niveaux de difficulté : facile, moyen et difficile. Un mot est choisi au hasard, les lettres sont cachées et vous devez deviner le mot en proposant une lettre après l'autre. À chaque fois que vous proposez une mauvaise lettre, une partie du dessin du pendu est affichée. Vous devez deviner le mot avant d'être pendu ! Vous avez 10 essais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KHangMan é un xogo baseado no coñecido xogo do enforcado. Está dirixido a rapaces de seis anos para riba. O xogo ten varias categorías de palabras coas que xogar (por exemplo «Animais», palabras relacionadas con animais) e tres categorías de dificultade: doado, medio e difícil.Escóllese unha palabra ao chou, agóchanse as letras e hai que adiviñar a palabra intentando letra a letra. Cada vez que se propón unha letra errada, debúxase unha parte dunha imaxe dun enforcado. Hai que adiviñar a palabra antes de que che colguen! Tes dez intentos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">KHangMan
הוא משחק שמבוסס על משחק האיש התלוי המפורסם. הוא מיועד לילדים מגיל שש ומעלה. למשחק יש מגוון קטגוריות של מילים שאפשר לשחק איתן, למשל: חיות (מילים של חיות) ושלוש קטגוריות קושי (קל, בינוני וקשה. מילה נבחרת באקראי, האותיות מוסתרות וצריך לנחש את המילה על ידי ניחוש של אות אחת אחרי השנייה. בכל פעם שניחשת אות שגויה, נוסף חלק לציור של האיש התלוי. צריך לנחש את המילה לפני שהאיש נתלה! יש לך 10 ניסיונות.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KHangMan adalah permainan yang didasarkan pada permainan hangman (algojo) yang terkenal. Ini ditujukan untuk anak-anak berusia enam tahun ke atas. Permainan ini memiliki beberapa kategori kata untuk dimainkan, misalnya: Hewan (nama-nama binatang) dan tiga kategori kesulitan: Mudah, Sedang dan Sukar. Sebuah kata dipilih secara acak, huruf-hurufnya disembunyikan, dan kamu harus menebak kata itu dengan mencoba huruf satu demi satu. Setiap kali kamu menebak huruf yang salah, bagian dari gambar algojo digambari. Kamu harus menebak kata sebelum digantung! Kamu memiliki 10 percobaan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KHangMan è basato sul ben noto gioco dell'impiccato. È pensato per i bambini da sei anni in su. Il gioco ha diverse categorie di parole con cui giocare tra cui Animali (parole di animali) e tre livelli di difficoltà: facile, medio e difficile. Una parola è scelta a caso, le lettere sono nascoste, e bisogna indovinare la parola provando una lettera alla volta. Ogni volta che provi una lettera sbagliata, compare parte dell'immagine di un impiccato. Devi indovinare la parola prima di farti impiccare! Hai a disposizione dieci tentativi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KHangMan ჩამოხრჩობანას თამაშია. ის 6+ ბავშვებისთვისაა განკუთვნილი. თამაშს სიტყვების რამდენიმე კატეგორია გააჩნია. მაგალთად: ცხოველები და სამი სირთულის კატეგორია: ადვილი, საშუალო და რთული. სიტყვები შემთხვევით შეირჩევა, ასოები დამალულია და სიტყვა ასოების ცდებით უნდა გამოიცნოთ. თითოეულ ჯერზე, რამდენჯერაც არასწორ ასოს აირჩევთ. ჩამოხრჩობილი კაცის სურთის ნაწილი გამოჩნდება. სიტყვა ჩამოხრჩობამდე უნდა გამოიცნოთ! სულ 10 ცდა გაქვთ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KHangMan은 잘 알려진 행맨 게임을 기반으로 한 게임입니다. 6세 이상의 어린이를 대상으로 합니다. 동물 등 다양한 주제별 단어를 선택할 수 있으며, 쉬움, 보통, 어려움 난이도를 선택할 수 있습니다. 단어가 무작위로 선택되고, 문자가 숨겨지며, 한 문자씩 시도하여 단어를 추측해야 합니다. 잘못된 글자를 추측 할 때마다 행맨 그림의 일부가 그려집니다. 사람이 완전히 그려지기 전에 단어를 추측해야 합니다! 총 10번 시도할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">KHangMan is en Speel, dat op dat begäng Speel „Galgenraden“ opbuut. Dat is för Kinners vun söss Johr af. Dat Speel hett en Reeg Woortkategorien, so as „Deerten“, un de dree Swoorheitstopen „Eenfach“, „Middel“ un „Swoor“. Dat Woort warrt tofällig utsöcht, de Bookstaven sünd toeerst versteken, un Du muttst de an na den annern raden. Raadst Du verkehrt, warrt en mehr Deel vun den Mann an'n Galgen maalt. Du muttst dat Woort raadt hebben, ehr he fardig is! Du hest 10 Versöök.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KHangMan is een spel dat is gebaseerd op het welbekende galgje. Het richt zich op kinderen van zes jaar en ouder. Het spel kent verschillende categorieën te spelen woorden waaronder: Dieren (dierenwoorden) en drie moeilijkheidsgraden, Eenvoudig, Middel en Moeilijk. Woorden worden willekeurig gekozen en de letters ervan worden verborgen. U raadt het woord door een voor een letters op te geven. Telkens als u een verkeerde letter raadt wordt er een gedeelte van de galg-afbeelding getekend. U moet het woord raden voordat u wordt opgehangen! U hebt 10 pogingen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KHangMan er eit spel basert på det klassiske hengdmann-spelet. Målgruppa er ungar frå seks år og oppover. Spelet har fleire ordkategoriar du kan velja mellom, for eksempel dyrenamn, og tre vanskegradar – lett, middels og vanskeleg. Datamaskina vel eit tilfeldig ord, og du må gjetta alle bokstavane i ordet. Kvar gong du gjettar ein bokstav som ikkje finst i ordet, vert delar av ein hengdmann teikna opp. Du må gjetta heile ordet før mannen vert hengd! Du har 10 forsøk.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KWisielec jest grą opartą na dobrze znanej grze w wisielca. Skierowana jest do dzieci w wieku powyżej sześciu lat. Gra ma kilka kategorii słów, którymi można zagrać, na przykład: Zwierzęta (słowa zwierzęce) i trzy kategorie trudności: Łatwa, Średnia i Trudna. Słowo jest wybierane losowo, litery są schowane, a ty musisz odgadnąć słowo próbując literkę po literce. Za każdym razem, gdy źle odgadniesz literkę, rysowana jest część wisielca. Musisz odgadnąć słowo przed powieszeniem! Masz 10 podejść.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KHangMan é um jogo baseado no conhecido jogo da forca. Destina-se a crianças com seis ou mais anos. O jogo tem diversas categorias de palavras com as quais jogar, como por exemplo: Animais (palavras de animais) e três categorias de dificuldade: Fácil, Médio e Difícil. É escolhida uma palavra de forma aleatória, as letras são escondidas e deverá adivinhar a palavra, escrevendo para tal uma letra após outra. De cada vez que errar uma letra, é desenhada parte da figura de um enforcado. Deverá desenhar a palavra antes que o enforcado fique completo! Tem 10 tentativas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KHangMan é um jogo baseado no conhecido jogo da forca. É destinado às crianças com seis ou mais anos. O jogo tem diversas categorias de palavras com as quais jogar, como por exemplo: Animais (palavras de animais) e três categorias de dificuldade: Fácil, Médio e Difícil. Uma palavra é escolhida aleatoriamente, sendo ocultas as suas letras, para que você possa adivinhar a palavra, digitando uma letra após a outra. Cada vez que escolher uma letra errada, é desenhada uma parte de um enforcado. Você deverá adivinhar a palavra antes de ficar enforcado! Você tem 10 tentativas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">KHangMan — игра, основанная на известной игре «Виселица». Она рассчитана на детей в возрасте 6 лет и старше. В игру входит несколько тематических наборов слов (например, «Животные» — названия животных), а также три набора слов разного уровня сложности («Простой», «Средний» и «Сложный»). Слова выбираются случайным образом, буквы закрыты: необходимо угадать слово, проверяя букву за буквой. Если буквы нет в слове, дорисовывается часть изображения виселицы. Слово нужно угадать до того, как виселица будет нарисована целиком! На угадывание слова даётся 10 попыток.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KHangMan je hra založená na známej hre Kat. Je určená pre deti od 6 rokov. Hra má niekoľko kategórií slov na hranie, napríklad zvieratá a tri stupne obtiažnosti: ľahká, stredná a ťažká. Slová sa vyberajú náhodne, písmená sa skryjú a musíte uhádnuť slovo skúšaním jedného písmena za druhým. Vždy keď neuhádnete písmeno, nakreslí sa časť obrázku kata. Musíte uhádnuť slovo skôr, ako vás kat popraví! Máte 10 pokusov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KHangMan je igra, ki temelji na dobro poznani igri vislic. Ciljna starostna skupina so otroci starejši od pet let. Igra ima številne kategorije besed (npr. Živali) in tri težavnostne stopnje: Lahko, Srednje in Težko. Beseda je naključno izbrana, črke so skrite, igralec pa mora besedo uganiti tako da posamično ugiba črke. Vsakič, ko je izbrana črka napačna, je izrisan del vislic. Besedo morate rešiti preden vas obesijo, pri tem pa vam je na voljo 10 poskusov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Hänga gubben är ett spel baserat på det välkända Hänga gubben spelet. Det är avsett för barn i åldrarna sex och uppåt. Spelet har flera ordkategorier att spela med, däribland Djur (djurord), och tre svårighetsnivåer: Lätt, Normal och Svår. Ett ord väljes slumpmässigt, bokstäverna är dolda och du måste gissa ordet genom att försöka med en bokstav i taget. Varje gång du gissar fel bokstav, ritas en del av bilden av en hängd gubbe. Du måste gissa ordet innan du blir hängd! Du har tio försök.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">K Adam Asmaca, iyi bilinen adam asmaca oyununa dayanır. Altı yaş ve üzeri çocuklara yöneliktir. Oyunun Hayvanlar (hayvan sözcükleri) gibi çeşitli sözcük kategorileri ve Kolay, Orta ve Zor olmak üzere üç zorluk düzeyi vardır. Bir sözcük harfleri gizli bir şekilde rastgele seçilir ve harf harf sözcüğü tahmin etmeniz gerekir. Her hatalı harf tahmininizde asılan adamın bir parçası çizilir. Tamamen asılmadan sözcüğü tahmin etmeniz gerekir. 10 deneme hakkınız vardır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KHangMan — це гра, заснована на відомій грі у ката. Її призначено для дітей віком від шести років. У грі є декілька категорій слів, зокрема Тварини (назви тварин), і три категорії складності: Проста, Середня і Складна. Слово вибирається випадковим чином, і всі його літери на початку сховані від вас. Ви повинні вгадати слово, послідовно намагаючись вгадати його літери. Кожного разу, коли ви називатимете літеру, якої у слові немає, домальовуватиметься частина зображення людини на шибениці. Ви повинні вгадати слово, перш ніж вас повісять! У вас десять спроб.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKHangMan is a game based on the well-known hangman game. It is aimed at children aged six and over. The game has several categories of words to play with, for example: Animals (animals words) and three difficulty categories: Easy, Medium and Hard. A word is picked at random, the letters are hidden, and you must guess the word by trying one letter after another. Each time you guess a wrong letter, part of a picture of a hangman is drawn. You must guess the word before being hanged! You have 10 tries.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KHangMan 是基于著名猜单词游戏的一款游戏，游戏对象为六岁以上儿童。本游戏有多种类型的单词可供游玩，例如：动物 (动物单词)，及三种不同难度的分类：简单、中等和困难。随机选择单词并隐藏字母，您必须通过一个个字母猜测的方式猜出单词。每次您猜错字母，就会画出吊颈公仔的一部分。您必须在吊颈公仔画完前猜出单词！您有十次机会。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KHangMan 是一套基於廣為人知的劊子手遊戲 hangman 的遊戲。目標是讓六歲以上的孩子們學習單字。這個遊戲有一些不同類別的單字，例如動物（跟動物相關的單字），有三種不同困難等級。隨機選取單字，但將字母隱藏，您必須一個個猜測字母。每次猜錯，就會劃出一部份被吊住的人，必須在人被吊死之前猜對！您會有十次機會。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/khangman</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=khangman</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=khangman</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=khangman&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Playing KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">لعبة الشنق</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Jugant al KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Jugant a KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hraní KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">At spille KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">KHangMan spielen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Παίζω Κρεμάλα</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Playing KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Ludante KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Jugando a KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">KHangManis mängimine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">KHangMan jokatzea</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">KHangManin pelaaminen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Partie de KHangMan en cours</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Xogando a KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">לשחק ב־KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Memainkan KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Giocare con KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">KHangMan-ის თამაში</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">KHangMan 플레이</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">KHangMan spelen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Spelar KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਕੇਹੈਂਗਮੈਨ ਖੇਡਣਾ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Granie w KWisielec</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">A jogar ao KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogando o KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Jucând KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Игра в KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Hranie KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Igra KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Spela Hänga gubben</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">K Adam Asmaca oynarken</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Гра у KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxPlaying KHangManxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">正在玩 KHangMan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">KHangMan 遊玩畫面</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/khangman/khangman.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>khangman</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.khangman.desktop</launchable>
  <releases>
    <release version="24.08.3" date="2024-11-07"/>
    <release version="24.08.2" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="24.08.1" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.0" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="24.05.2" date="2024-07-04"/>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23"/>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
